(police sirens)
Loki:
You were made to be ruled
(cars exploding)
(military men aiming their guns followed by a military jeep with rubble surrounding them)
Loki:
In the end,
it'll be every man for himself
(cars exploding)
(helicopter whirring)
Agent Coulson:
What do we do?
(Dramatic rock music playing in the background)
Nick Fury:
We get ready.
There was an idea
Nick Fury:
to bring together
a group of remarkable people.
Nick Fury:
So when we needed them,
they could fight the battles
Nick Fury:
that we never could.
Gentleman,
Nick Fury:
What are you prepared to do?
Tony Stark:
No offence but I don't play well with others
Steve Rogers:
Big man in a suit of armour. Take that away, what are you?
Tony Stark:
A genius, billionaire, playboy, philanthropist
Thor:
(Laughing)
(rock music playing)
Tony Stark:
If we can't protect the earth,
you can be damn sure we'll avenge it.
(Ironman flies across the city)
Tony Stark:
Doctor Banner, your work in unparralelled
And I'm a huge fan of the way you lose control and turn into an enormous green rage monster
Bruce Banner:
Thanks.