I want to talk about the Disney plus series,
Loki, yes, you're getting your own show.
Unbelievable. This is giant.
This is it. I mean, that's great.
Yeah, it's it is it is amazing.
I never expected it.
You know, I auditioned for the for the first
Thor film 10 years ago in 2009.
And I just thought I was auditioning for a
movie, you know, an interesting part
interesting movie back then.
The Marvel Universe was only they just made
Iron Man.
And I thought, oh, I'll have a go, didn't
expect.
I didn't expect to be casted at all.
So I can't believe I've got my own show.
It's so exciting. We go into production next
year and.
And that's about as much as I can tell you,
because
I know the way Marvel plays it, you're not
allowed to tell me anything at all.
But you you were tell me backstage that when
you auditioned for Thor, you actually
auditioned for Thor.
I did. Yes, I did.
I'm basically at the time they were what
they were looking for, sort of less well
established actors so that the audience
didn't have an association.
They were like they just wanted people to
see these new characters, these new actors in
the band. And I they would be the remit
was.
If you're over six foot and you've got blond
hair and, you know, you could come and have a
pop at it. So I actually just I never
auditioned for Loki.
I only ever auditioned for Thor, which is
nuts.
And how long
Did the audition
Process I mean, it was about three months.
Was you for a second you go, this is really I
could be Thor
For a second for a little over a second.